

about skills

// As a former advertising Account Supervisor, advertising taught me about great design while my time as a Web Developer at Igloo Software has instilled in me a passion for accessibility. Combined, my experiences have helped me to develop a user focused mind set while developing pixel perfect UI. // JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, jQuery, CSS, Sass, HTML, Accessible Web Development

experience

// Uberflip - Toronto, ON Team Lead & Software Developer,

October 2019 - Present

Software Developer,

April 2019 - October 2019

Front End Developer,

April 2018 - April 2019

// Igloo Software - Kitchener, ON Web Developer,

September 2016 - April 2018

// **ds+p** - Toronto, ON Account Supervisor,

August 2015 - December 2015

Account Manager,

July 2013 - July 2015

Account Coordinator,

March 2012 - June 2013

- // As a team lead actively working with team manager to run daily team standups and coordinate additional tasks when needed, such as helping with team demos and unblocking tickets
- // As a software developer, working as a member of a scrum team focused on developing accessible modern application UI using Liquid, TypeScript, Webpack, and Sass
- // Worked on a client facing development team to deliver maintainable and scalable custom solutions and themes for clients using HTML, Sass, JavaScript and ¡Query
- // Supported the client success team by demonstrating product customizations and providing product specific developer training to clients and customers as needed
- // Worked with senior clients to develop cross-media campaigns to meet key business objectives, including doubling in-store sales year-over-year
- // Worked closely with creative teams and designers to complete and deliver multiple cross-media campaigns on time and within budget to drive results to increase brand awareness and drive site traffic, in some cases doubling industry benchmarks

volunteer

// Ladies Learning Code, Toronto, ON Mentor.

April 2016 - February 2020

// Supported instructors by providing one-on-one direction to students and helped students debug code for Intro to HTML & CSS and Intro to JavaScript workshops

education

- // Bridge Toronto, ON, Software Development, Completed September 2019
- // Bitmaker Toronto, ON, Web Development, Completed March 2016
- // George Brown College Toronto, ON, Continuing Education Certificate, Web Development, Graduated March 2015
- // King's University College at the University of Western Ontario London, ON, Bachelors of Arts Degree, Honours Specialization History, Graduated April 2007